Reading mode: Light Dark

Site update:

We will be making some enhancements to our login process, [click here](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67698210) for more information

Privacy Notice of Digital Photography Review
============================================

**Last updated: April 23, 2024.**

We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. Please note that Gear Patrol, LLC operates DPReview. This Privacy Notice describes how Gear Patrol, LLC doing business as DPReview ("DPReview," "we," "us" or "our") collects and processes your personal information through DPReview websites, services, and applications that reference this Privacy Notice (together the "DPReview Services"). **By using the DPReview Services, you are consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

#### Additional State-Specific Privacy Disclosures

Residents of California, Connecticut, Colorado, Utah and Virginia click [here](#statedisclosures) to read additional state-specific privacy disclosures.

### What Personal Information About Users Does DPReview Collect?

We collect your personal information in order to provide and continually improve our services and your experience at DPReview.

Here are the types of personal information we collect:

* **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you provide in relation to DPReview Services. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our DPReview Services. [See examples of what provided information we collect.](#collectedinfo)
* **Automatic Information:** We automatically collect and store certain types of information about your use of DPReview Services, including information about your interaction with content and services available through DPReview Services. Like many websites, we use "cookies" and other unique identifiers, and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser or device accesses DPReview Services and other content served by or on behalf of DPReview on other websites. [See examples of what information we automatically collect and store.](#autoinfo)
* **Information from Other Sources:** We might receive information about you from other sources, such as your name and email address when you sign in to DPReview using a third-party login service. [See additional examples of the information we receive from other sources.](#othersources)

### For What Purposes Does DPReview Use Your Personal Information?

We use your personal information to operate, provide, develop, and improve the products and services that we offer our customers. These purposes include:

* **Provide, troubleshoot, and improve DPReview Services.** We use your personal information to provide the DPReview Services, process payments, enhance functionality, analyze performance, fix errors, and improve the usability and effectiveness of the DPReview Services.
* **Recommendations and personalization.** We use your personal information to recommend features, content, products, and services that might be of interest to you, identify your preferences, and personalize your experience with DPReview Services.
* **Comply with legal obligations.** In certain cases, we collect and use your personal information to comply with laws.
* **Communicate with you.** We use your personal information to communicate with you in relation to DPReview Services via different channels (e.g., e-mail or on-site forums).
* **Advertising.** We use your personal information to display interest-based ads for features, products, and services that might be of interest to you. To learn more, please see [What About Advertising?](#aboutads).
* **Fraud Prevention.** We use personal information to prevent and detect fraud and abuse in order to protect the security of our customers, DPReview, and others.

### What About Cookies and Other Identifiers?

We use cookies, pixels, and other technologies (collectively "cookies") to recognize your browser or device, learn more about your interests, and provide you with essential features and services and for additional purposes, including:

* Recognizing you when you sign-in to our services. This allows us to provide you with content recommendations, display personalized content, and provide other customized features and services.
* Keeping track of your specified preferences. This allows us to honor your preferences, such as whether or not you would like to see interest-based ads. You may set your preferences for interest-based ads [here](https://www.dpreview.com/misc/privacypreferences).
* Conducting research and diagnostics to improve DPReview's content and services.
* Preventing fraudulent activity.
* Improving security.
* Delivering content, including ads.
* Reporting. This allows us to measure and analyze the performance of our services.

DPReview's cookies allow you to take advantage of some of DPReview's essential features. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to contribute content or use any DPReview Services that require you to sign in.

Approved third parties may also set cookies when you interact with DPReview Services. Third parties include providers of measurement and analytics services, social media networks, and advertising companies. Third parties use cookies in the process of delivering content, including ads relevant to your interests, to measure the effectiveness of their ads, and to perform services on behalf of DPReview. We and our approved third parties may use first-party cookies (like analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (like advertising cookies) together to serve you with ads.

You can manage browser cookies through your browser settings. The 'Help' feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, how to block cookies, and when cookies will expire. If you block all cookies on your browser, neither we nor third parties will transfer cookies to your browser. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some features and services may not work.

### Does DPReview Share Your Personal Information?

Information about our users is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling our users' personal information to others. We share user information with our affiliates that follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice, and as described below.

* **Transactions involving Third Parties:** We make available to you services provided by third parties. You can tell when a third party is involved in your transactions, and we share users' personal information related to those transactions with that third party.
* **Third-Party Service Providers:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing payments, removing repetitive information from user lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and transmitting content. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
* **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy other businesses or services or enter into a merger or reorganization or another transaction in which a third party invests in or acquires control of our business or assets (in whole or in part). In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the user consents otherwise). Also, in the event that all or substantially all of the assets related to DPReview.com are acquired, user information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
* **Protection of DPReview and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our [Conditions of Use](https://www.dpreview.com/misc/termsandconditions) and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of DPReview, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when personal information about you might be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

### What About Advertising?

* **Third-Party Advertising and Links to Other Websites:** DPReview Services may include third-party advertising and links to other websites and apps. Third-party advertising partners may collect information about you when you interact with their content, advertising, and services. For more information about third-party advertising at DPReview, including interest-based ads, please read the section on [Interest-Based Ads](#interestbasedads). To adjust your advertising preferences, please go to the [Privacy Preferences](https://www.dpreview.com/misc/privacypreferences) page.
* **Use of Third-Party Advertising Services:** We provide ad companies with information that allows them to serve you with more useful and relevant ads and to measure their effectiveness. For example, we may use an advertising identifier like a cookie or other device identifier. Some ad companies also use this information to serve you relevant ads from other advertisers. You can learn more about how to opt-out of interest-based advertising by going to the [Privacy Preferences](https://www.dpreview.com/misc/privacypreferences) page.
* DPReview is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a Raptive ("Raptive") for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and Raptive will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about Raptive's data usage, [click here](https://raptive.com/creator-advertising-privacy-statement/).

### How Secure Is Information About Me?

We design our systems with your security and privacy in mind.

* We work to protect the security of your personal information during transmission by using encryption protocols and software.
* We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in connection with collection, storage, and disclosure of personal customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.
* Despite our efforts to ensure security, we cannot guarantee or warrant that your personal information will not be accessed, acquired, disclosed, altered or destroyed by an unauthorized person or as a result of a breach of our security safeguards or those of our hosting provider or other vendors or service providers. We cannot ensure the security of any data transmitted to us over the internet. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure by us of personal information.
* It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computers, devices, and applications. We recommend using a unique password for your DPReview account that is not used for other online accounts. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

### What Information Can I Access?

You can access your information, including your user name, location, and profile information in your account settings.

### What Choices Do I Have?

If you have any questions as to how we collect and use your personal information, please contact us through [this form](https://www.dpreview.com/feedback?category=general&url=https%3a%2f%2fwww.dpreview.com%2fmisc%2fprivacypolicy). Many of our DPReview Services also include settings that provide you with options as to how your information is being used.

* As described above, you can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of the DPReview Services.
* You can add, update or correct certain information on your profile such as those referenced in [What Information Can I Access?](#accessinfo) When you update or correct information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
* If you do not want to receive e-mail or other communications from us, please log in to your account and adjust your preferences in your user account settings.
* If you do not want to see interest-based ads, please adjust your [Privacy Preferences](https://www.dpreview.com/misc/privacypreferences).
* The Help feature on most browsers and devices will tell you how to prevent your browser or device from accepting new cookies or other identifiers, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to block cookies altogether. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some essential features of DPReview Services, we recommend that you leave them turned on.
* Most devices provide users with the ability to change device permissions (e.g., disable/access location services). For most devices, these controls are located in the device's setting menu. If you have questions about how to change your device permissions on devices manufactured by third parties, we recommend you contact your mobile service carrier or your device manufacturer.
* If you want to browse our websites without linking the browsing history to your account, you may do so by logging out of your account and blocking cookies on your browser.
* If you want to request access to and/or delete your personal information, please log in to your account and complete [this form](https://www.dpreview.com/delete-account).

You may also make a request to access, delete or correct your personal information by contacting us through [this form](https://my.datasubject.com/AzqJWOTOhUG2o2977/24101) and specifying your request. We may ask for information to verify your identity. We may deny your request if we cannot verify your identity or if otherwise permitted under applicable law. Depending on your data choices, certain services may be limited or unavailable.

### Are Children Allowed to Use DPReview Services?

DPReview Services are not intended for use by children under the age of 16. If you are under 16, you may not sign up for DPReview Services or submit information about yourself to DPReview.

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to use DPReview Services, your use and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Notice and our [Conditions of Use](https://www.dpreview.com/misc/termsandconditions), including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Washington.

We operate from the United States and the personal information we collect or receive is stored and processed in the United States and may be processed in other countries around the world subject to the provisions of this Privacy Notice. You consent to the transfer, processing and storage of personal information in the United States and any other country in which we, our affiliates or service providers maintain facilities or process personal information. The United States and such other countries may not have the same data protection laws as your home jurisdiction and may afford materially less protections for your personal information than your home jurisdiction.

If you have any concern about privacy at DPReview, please send us a thorough description to our [customer service team](https://www.dpreview.com/feedback?category=general&url=https%3a%2f%2fwww.dpreview.com%2fmisc%2fprivacypolicy), and we will try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice will change also. You should check our websites frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

### Examples of Information Collected

#### Information You Give Us When You Use DPReview Services

You provide information to us when you:

* search for information on DPReview Services;
* subscribe to DPReview Services;
* stream, view, or use content on a device or through a service or application on a device;
* provide information in your user account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when using DPReview services) or in your DPReview profile or posts;
* configure your settings on, provide data access permissions for, or interact with DPReview Services;
* submit content contributions;
* communicate with us by email or the DPReview Help Center;
* complete a questionnaire or a promotional entry form;
* vote in a poll;
* upload or stream images or videos;
* employ our notification services.

As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as:

* identifying information such as your name, e-mail address, physical address, and phone number;
* payment information;
* your age;
* your gender;
* your location information;
* your IP address;
* your profession and educational background;
* your physical attributes;
* your bio;
* your website;
* your signature;
* content of reviews, posts to on-site forums, and e-mails to us;
* personal description and photographs you submit about yourself;
* images and videos uploaded to DPReview Services; and
* information and documents regarding identity (e.g., driver's license numbers).

#### Automatic Information

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include:

* the internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet;
* login, e-mail address, and password;
* the location of your device or computer;
* content interaction information, such as content streams, and playback details, and network details for streaming quality, including information about your internet service provider;
* device metrics such as when a device is in use, application usage, connectivity data, and any errors or event failures;
* DPReview Service metrics (e.g., the occurrences of technical errors, your interactions with service features and content, your settings preferences, location of your device running an application, information about uploaded images and files such as the file name of your images);
* version and time zone settings;
* purchase and content use history;
* the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our websites, including date and time; content you viewed or searched for; and
* page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, and page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs).

We may also use device identifiers, cookies, and other technologies on devices, applications, and our web pages to collect browsing, usage, or other technical information.

#### Information from Other Sources

Examples of information we receive from other sources include:

* biographical information;
* images and videos uploaded to DPReview Services;
* reviews; and
* press interviews and media articles.

### Additional State-Specific Privacy Disclosures

This additional state-specific privacy disclosure ("Disclosure") effective June 12, 2023 supplements this Privacy Notice for users located in California, Connecticut, Colorado, Utah and Virginia.

1. **Categories of personal information collected.** The personal information that DPReview collects, or has collected from consumers in the twelve months prior to the effective date of this Disclosure, falls into the following categories, depending on which DPReview Service is used:
    * identifiers such as your name, user ID, email address, IP address, your DPReview account log-in information, or a government issued identifier (e.g., if you submit such identifier for identity verification purposes)
    * personal information, such as a credit card number, or other payment information;
    * information that may reveal age, gender, race, sexual orientation, or other protected classifications, for example if you choose to provide such information in your DPReview profile or posts;
    * commercial information, such as products or services you purchased, obtained or considered, or other of your purchasing histories or tendencies;
    * education information, for example if you choose to provide such information in your DPReview profile or posts;
    * Internet or other electronic network activity information, including content interaction information, such as content streams and playback details;
    * geolocation data (which may in some cases constitute precise geolocation information), such as the location of your device if you agree to provide this information;
    * audio or visual information, such as images and videos uploaded in your DPReview profile or posts;
    * professional information; and
    * inference data, including inferences derived from other information we collect (including usage data).
2. **Categories of personal information disclosed for a business purpose.** The personal information that DPReview disclosed to the third parties identified in the ["Does DPReview Share Your Personal Information?"](#infosharing) section of this Privacy Notice about consumers for a business purpose in the twelve months prior to the effective date of this Disclosure falls into the following categories, depending on which DPReview Service is used:
    * identifiers such as your name and email address, for example if we work with a third party to fulfill a promotional prize;
    * personal information, such as a credit card number or other payment information, for example if we use a third-party payment processor;
    * information that may reveal age, gender, race, sexual orientation, or other protected classifications, for example if you choose to submit such information in your DPReview profile or posts;
    * commercial information, such as products or services you purchased, obtained or considered, or other of your purchasing histories or tendencies;
    * education information, if you choose to submit such information in your DPReview profile or posts;
    * internet or other electronic network activity information, such as if we use a service provider to help us gather crash reports for analyzing the health of our services;
    * audio or visual information, such as your profile photo if you choose to submit such information in your DPReview profile or posts; and
    * professional information if you choose to submit such information in your DPReview profile or posts.
3. **Advertising.** As explained in the ["What about Advertising?"](#aboutads) section in this Privacy Notice, DPReview shares limited information to help ensure you receive more useful and relevant ads and to measure their effectiveness. Any personal information DPReview may have shared for the purpose of targeted advertising or cross-context behavioral advertising (as that term is defined by the California Consumer Privacy Act) in the twelve months prior to the effective date of this Disclosure falls into the following categories:
    
    * identifiers such as a cookie, a device identifier, or a code derived from applying irreversible cryptography to other information like an email address; we never share your name or other information that directly identifies you.
    * internet or other electronic network activity information, such as whether you downloaded an app or other measures of ad effectiveness.
    
    The categories of third parties with whom DPReview may share personal information for the purpose of targeted advertising or cross-context behavioral advertising are identified in the ["Does DPReview Share Your Personal Information?"](#infosharing) and ["What About Advertising?"](#aboutads) sections of the DPReview Privacy Notice. DPReview also processes personal information for the purposes of targeted advertising and cross-context behavioral advertising. DPReview does not share for cross-context behavioral advertising or targeted advertising purposes the personal information of consumers under 16 years of age.
4. **Your Data Rights:** You may have certain data rights under applicable privacy law in your home jurisdiction.
    * You may have the right to request information about the collection of your personal information by DPReview, to access your personal information in a portable format, and to correct or delete your personal information. For requests to access and/or delete your personal information, you may log in to your account and complete [this form](https://www.dpreview.com/delete-account). To make any data rights request, if you do not have an account, or you are an authorized agent please submit your specific request through [this form](https://my.datasubject.com/AzqJWOTOhUG2o2977/24101). To ensure the security of your DPReview account, we will generally ask you to verify your request using the contact information you have already provided. We may deny your request if we cannot verify your identity or if otherwise permitted under applicable law.
    * You may have the right to opt out of the processing of your personal data for targeted advertising or the sharing of your personal information for cross-context behavioral advertising. To do so, please click [Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information](https://www.dpreview.com/misc/privacypreferences).
    * You may have the right to direct us to not share your personal data with third parties for third parties' direct marketing purposes. You have the option to do so from [this form](https://my.datasubject.com/AzqJWOTOhUG2o2977/24101) by opting out from targeted advertisting.
    * You may also have the right to appeal the denial of any of these rights by submitting a form that will be provided to you if we deny a data request.Depending on your data choices, certain services may be limited or unavailable.
5. **No sale of personal information.** In the twelve months prior to the effective date of this Disclosure, DPReview has not sold any personal information of consumers, as those terms are defined under the California Consumer Privacy Act.
6. **Sensitive Personal Information Disclosure.** The categories of data that DPReview collects and discloses for a business purpose include "sensitive personal information" (and similar terms, as defined by applicable privacy law). DPReview does not use or disclose sensitive personal information for any purpose not expressly permitted by applicable privacy law.
7. **Retention Disclosure.** We keep your personal information to enable your continued use of DPReview Services, for as long as it is required in order to fulfill the relevant purposes described in this Privacy Notice, as permitted or as may be required by law, or as otherwise communicated to you.
8. **Non-discrimination Statement.** DPReview will not discriminate against any consumer for exercising their rights under the applicable privacy laws of their jurisdiction.
9. **De-identified Data Disclosure.** DPReview may use de-identified data in some instances. DPReview either maintains such data without attempting to re-identify it or treats such data as personal data subject to applicable law.

### Interest-Based Ads

Interest-based ads are sometimes referred to as personalized or targeted ads. We show interest-based ads to display features, products, and services that might be of interest to you.

#### What sort of information do we use to show interest-based ads?

To serve you interest-based ads, we use information such as your interactions with DPReview Services or content.

As is common in the advertising industry, we use cookies, pixels, and other technologies (collectively, "cookies"), which enable us to understand the effectiveness of the interest-based ads we show you by measuring what ads are clicked or viewed, and to provide you with more useful and relevant ads. For example, if we know what ads are shown to your browser we can be careful not to show the same ads repeatedly.

#### How do we work with third parties to show you interest-based ads?

We work with third parties, such as advertisers, publishers, social media networks, search engines, ad serving companies, and advertising companies working on their behalf, to improve the relevance of ads we serve. Advertisers and other third parties may assume that users who interact with or click on an interest-based ad or content are part of the group that the ad or content is directed towards (for example, users in a particular geographical area or users who purchased or browsed for a certain camera). Some third-parties may provide us information about you (such as demographic information or sites where you have been shown ads) from offline and online sources that we may use to provide you more relevant and useful advertising. For more information on the third parties we work with to show you interest-based ads, and to set your preferences for interest-based ads, visit the [Privacy Preferences](https://www.dpreview.com/misc/privacypreferences) page.

Third party advertisers or advertising companies working on their behalf sometimes use cookies in the process of delivering content, including ads, directly to your browser or device, and they may automatically receive an IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies to measure the effectiveness of their ads, show you more relevant advertising content, and perform services on behalf of us. For information on how to control and delete cookies (including third party cookies) please visit the [Cookies](#cookies) section of this Privacy Notice.

#### Advertising Preferences

We offer you choices about receiving interest-based ads. If you choose not to receive interest-based ads, you will still see ads in the DPR Services but they will not be based on your interests. Please visit the [Privacy Preferences](https://www.dpreview.com/misc/privacypreferences) page to learn how to set your preferences.

You can also generally opt out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1) or who follow the [Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN) by visiting the opt out pages on the NAI website and DAA website.

Featured Videos

Latest reviews

|     |     |
| --- | --- |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| [](https://www.dpreview.com/reviews/fujifilm-x100vi-review) | [Fujifilm X100VI review](https://www.dpreview.com/reviews/fujifilm-x100vi-review) | 87% |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| [](https://www.dpreview.com/reviews/panasonic-lumix-dc-s5ii-review) | [Panasonic Lumix DC-S5II review](https://www.dpreview.com/reviews/panasonic-lumix-dc-s5ii-review) | 90% |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| [](https://www.dpreview.com/reviews/panasonic-lumix-dc-g9-ii-review) | [Panasonic Lumix DC-G9 II](https://www.dpreview.com/reviews/panasonic-lumix-dc-g9-ii-review) | 87% |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |

[See all reviews](https://www.dpreview.com/reviews) »

Finished challenges

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Ready to Pounce by ltphoto1  <br>from A Big Year 2024 | american bald eagle with snow falling by summicron  <br>from Birds - Wingspan | GEICO Skytypers by pcrossing  <br>from Your Favorite Two Photos and Why | Carnival by Marzio5  <br>from Masks #2 |

[Discover more challenges](https://www.dpreview.com/challenges/) »

Most popular cameras

[Popular interchangable lens cameras](https://www.dpreview.com/products/slrs/statistics) »

[Popular compact cameras](https://www.dpreview.com/products/compacts/statistics) »

Features

[In-depth testingLatest Camera Reviews](https://www.dpreview.com/reviews "Latest Camera Reviews")[Beyond the studio testsFeature Articles and Videos](https://www.dpreview.com/features "Feature Articles and Videos")[see how we seeSample Galleries](https://www.dpreview.com/sample-galleries "Sample Galleries")[Throwback ThursdayClassic Cameras from Days Past](https://www.dpreview.com/tag/throwback-thursday "Classic Cameras from Days Past")[What's that Noise?Shedding some light on the sources of noise](https://www.dpreview.com/tag/noise "Shedding some light on the sources of noise")

Top threads

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| 97  | [Is Fujifilm losing its way?](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67713928) |
| 37  | [\* The Weekly Image Thread 24 05 20 #870 \*](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67716457) |
| 28  | [Hi ISO never looked this good](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67714777) |
| 27  | [New to OMDS and rant](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67714168) |
| 27  | [When images can't be believed anymore,](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67714346) |
| 24  | [GF 100-200 vs XF 50-140](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67714527) |
| 22  | [OM1 Digital Teleconverter](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67714661) |
| 22  | [Carrying a body with heavy lens, basic questions](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67715712) |
| 21  | [Clear filters - yeah or nay?](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67714357) |
| 20  | [ASP-C mode. Who’s using it and why?](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67714019) |
| 20  | [Lucky walkabout](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67715021) |
| 20  | [Testing exposure](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67715564) |
| 18  | [Panasonic G90 - Battery Life, is this behaviour normal?](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67714680) |
| 18  | [How to get rid of cables / ropes?](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67716537) |
| 17  | [\*\* Weekly Sigma Photos Thread 20 May - 26 May 26 2024 \*\*](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67715641) |
| 17  | [last week (5) - various](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67715261) |
| 16  | [Stop me from buying refurb Z50 w/lens for $600.](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67716758) |
| 15  | [Is the new XF 16-50 f2.8-4.8 the best kit lens ever offered with an APS-C camera?](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67715519) |
| 15  | [Safari camera/lens suggestions](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67714511) |
| 14  | [Don’t ever take that first drink!](https://www.dpreview.com/forums/post/67714970) |

Follow us

About

Editorial content

Cameras & Lenses

Community

All content, design, and layout are Copyright © 1998–2024 Digital Photography Review All Rights Reserved.  
Reproduction in whole or part in any form or medium without specific written permission is prohibited.  
When you use DPReview links to buy products, the site may earn a commission.
